const Questions= [

{
  prompt: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include?\n (a) strings\n (b) boolean\n (c) number\n (d) lens",

  answers: "d"

},

{
  prompt: "The condition of an if/else statement is enclosed with?\n (a) brackets\n (b) elipses\n (c) parenthesis\n (d) hugs",

  answers: "c"

},

{
  prompt: "What does 'return' do in a fucntion?\n (a) nothing\n (b) runs the function again\n (c) voids entire function\n (d) returns specified value from function",

  answers: "d"

},

{
  prompt: "Which of the following is true about variable naming conventions in JavaScript?\n (a) variables must begin with a letter or underscore character\n (b) variables are case sensitive\n (c) Both a & b\n (d) Neither a or b",

  answers: "c"

},

{
  prompt: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include?\n (a) strings\n (b) boolean\n (c) number\n (d) lens",

  answers: "d"

},

{
  prompt: "Which of the follwing type of variable is only visible in it's defined function?\n (a) global\n (b) lcoal\n (c) Both a & b\n (d) Neither a or b",

  answers: "b"

},

{
  prompt: "Which function gives the length of a variable?\n (a) .total\n (b) .len\n (c) .length\n (d) .space",

  answers: "c"

},

{
  prompt: "Which function returns an integer of a string argument?\n (a) parseInt()\n (b) toString()\n (c) function()\n (d) toFixed()",

  answers: "a"

},

{
  prompt: "Which keyword is used to define a variable in Javascript?\n (a) var\n (b) let\n (c) Both a&b\n (d) Neither a or b",

  answers: "c"

},

{
  prompt: "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML IDs using Javascript?\n (a) getElementbyI()\n (b) getElementbyClassName()\n (c) Both a & b\n (d) Neither a or b",

  answers: "c"

},

{
  prompt: "How can a datatype be declard a constant type?\n (a) const\n (b) var\n (c) let\n (d) constant",

  answers: "a"

},

{
  prompt: "JavaSCript is an ____ language?\n (a) Object-Oriented\n (b) Object-Based\n (c) Procedural\n (d) None of the above",

  answers: "a"

},












]

let timeleft = document.querySelector("#timeleft");
let startButton = document.querySelector("#start");


startButton.addEventListener("click", function() {
 
});


